[{
        "question": "What is 0.3 + 0.45?",
        "answer": "0.75",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 0.52 - 0.14?",
        "answer": "0.38",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 0.7 * 0.5?",
        "answer": "0.35",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 1.5 รท 0.5?",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Write 2/5 as a decimal.",
        "answer": "0.4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Write 0.6 as a fraction.",
        "answer": "3/5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Round 0.79 to the nearest tenth.",
        "answer": "0.8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Round 0.934 to the nearest hundredth.",
        "answer": "0.93",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Convert 7.25 to a mixed number.",
        "answer": "7 1/4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Convert 3 3/10 to a decimal.",
        "answer": "3.3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 0.08 * 100?",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 4.5 รท 100?",
        "answer": "0.045",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 0.75 as a percentage?",
        "answer": "75%",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 40% as a decimal?",
        "answer": "0.4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is greater: 0.25 or 0.125?",
        "answer": "0.25",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is smaller: 0.6 or 0.65?",
        "answer": "0.6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Order these decimals from smallest to largest: 0.3, 0.15, 0.45",
        "answer": "0.15, 0.3, 0.45",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Order these decimals from largest to smallest: 0.72, 0.9, 0.7",
        "answer": "0.9, 0.72, 0.7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Add 0.58 and 2.09",
        "answer": "2.67",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Subtract 0.035 from 0.5",
        "answer": "0.465",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]